centraldispatch.com 2015-03-16

# Privacy Policy for Dealertrack CentralDispatch, Inc. | The Auto Industry's Vehicle Shipping Marketplace

This Privacy Policy was last updated: January 14, 2013.

PLEASE READ THE FOLLOWING. THE FOLLOWING POLICIES CONCERN YOUR PRIVACY WHEN YOU ACCESS OR OTHERWISE USE THIS WEBSITE AND ITS SERVICES.

The websites jtracker.com and centraldisptach.com (individually, “ **Site** ”) are owned and operated by Dealertrack, Inc. and Dealertrack CentralDispatch, Inc., respectively (collectively " **Dealertrack** ", " **we** ", " **us** "). Your privacy is important to Dealertrack, and this privacy policy explains the data collection and privacy practices for users of the Site (“ **Privacy Policy** ”). This Privacy Policy does not pertain to information collected on any other site owned by Dealertrack, its subsidiaries or other businesses.

By visiting and using the Site, you agree to abide by the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy, and you consent to the collection, use and disclosure of your personal information by Company in accordance with the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy. By visiting, using and/or registering with the Site, the individual person taking such action (i) agrees with, and agrees to comply with, this Privacy Policy and any updates, revisions or modifications to it and (ii) represents and warrants that he or she has the legal right to do so.

Dealertrack reserves the right to change, modify, add, or remove provisions of this Privacy Policy. Any changes to this Privacy Policy will be posted here, and we encourage you to check back from time to time to ensure continuing familiarity with the most current version of our Privacy Policy. At the top of this page, we will indicate the "Effective Date" of the most recent version of the Privacy Policy; this will allow you to determine whether the Privacy Policy has been revised since your previous visit to the Site.

IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY TERMS OF USE OR SERVICE FOR THE SITE, PLEASE DO NOT PROVIDE COMPANY WITH ANY INFORMATION AND DO NOT USE THE SITE.

###### I. What Information We Collect.

  * **Non-Personally Identifiable Information.** When you enter this Site, information is gathered from your Internet browser. This information may include your IP address and log files (which allows us to determine the identity of your Internet Service Provider), your operating system and the type of browser software that you are using to access this Site. All information obtained from your browser is anonymous, and no personal information is ever transmitted to us in this manner. Company may also automatically collect and record information about your visit (through the use of cookies, web beacons and otherwise) as part of its analysis of the use of the Site and its performance. A "cookie" is a small text file that a website can place on your computer's hard drive in order, for example, to retain your preferences and/or registration information for your next visit to that Web site. The cookie transmits this information back to that website’s operator. You can choose not to receive a cookie file by enabling your web browser to refuse cookies or prompt you before accepting a cookie. Note that refusing to accept cookies may impact the performance of a website. In addition, when a web page is requested from the Site, Company may record the time, date and URL of the request and information on the browser being used.
  * **Personally Identifiable Information.** Portions this Site are "registration-required" pages that may require you to submit personal information before we grant you access. In addition, if you submit an inquiry to us via the “Contact Us” link, you may be required to submit personal information. Such information may include your name, company name, address, e-mail address, phone numbers and other identifying information about you and your company, including, but not limited to, Employer Identification Number (EIN), Motor Carrier number, insurance and license information and business references (individually or collectively, “ **Your Information** ”). In some instances, when submitting a W-9 as part of your document packet, you may have the opportunity to provide a Social Security number as an alternative to Tax Identification number by electronic facsimile or other means. We request that you do not use Social Security numbers on W-9 forms with any information packets provided to us and we will endeavor to prevent such forms from being accepted onto the Site. Note that such transmissions do not involve encryption or other secure means of transfer. You represent and warrant that you have all rights necessary to submit Your Information and to provide the consents and other rights granted with respect thereto under this Privacy Policy. You are responsible for the accuracy of Your Information. You agree that Company is only a facilitator of the Site and has no responsibility for the accuracy of Your Information.

###### II. How We Use Information We Collect.

  * **Non-Personally Identifiable Information.** We may use non-personally identifiable information to measure the number of visits, average time spent on the Site and pages viewed as well as to diagnose problems with our servers and to administer the Site. We may then use this information to analyze and improve the features and functionality of this Site. Please note that we also may match non-personally identifiable information, such as your IP address, to your personally identifiable information in order to augment our ability to administer, and to optimize, the Site for you. This data is not linked to any personal information or used to personally identify you, but may be aggregated to enable Company to perform business analytics, analyze trends, administer the Site, optimize the performance of the site, and gather information regarding where visits to the Site originate, how often the Site is visited and what parts of the Site are visited most often. The server logs may include information such as your Web request, Internet Protocol address, browser type, browser language, and the date and time of your visit.
  * **Personally Identifiable Information.** You acknowledge and agree that Company may collect, use, display, transmit, monitor, store and disclose Your Information as set forth in this Privacy Policy and in connection with the Company’s business, products and services and operation of the Site and that Company does not assume any responsibility or liability for (i) any information you submit to the Site or (ii) your or third parties' use or misuse of information transmitted or received using the Site. By providing Your Information, you agree and consent to Company sharing certain of Your Information for any reason and to any person or entity, including, but not limited to, within our company, with third parties who subscribe to this Site, with third parties who work with us on marketing, product development, service enhancement and other similar matters. Company may sell, transfer or otherwise share some or all of its assets, including Your Information, in connection with a merger, acquisition, reorganization, restructuring or sale of assets or in the event of bankruptcy or insolvency. Without limiting the generality of the foregoing, we may use Your Information as follows:
    * **Site** : We may use Your Information to better tailor your Web site experience to your interests, and to send you information about Dealertrack and its services as well as promotional material on behalf of some of our partners. We use other personally identifiable information that you provide to us to show you content in which you may be interested and to display the content according to your preferences. We will also share this information within the Dealertrack business family in order to enhance your experience on this and other Dealertrack Web sites.
    * **Administrative Matters** : Dealertrack reserves the right to contact you in the event of a change in the Site's Terms of Service and/or this Privacy Policy, or to notify you of other administrative matters in connection with the Site (e.g., contacting you to facilitate, complete or confirm a transaction).
    * **Transactions With E-Commerce Partners, Vendors and Advertisers** : When you provide Your Information to one of our Site's e-commerce partners, vendors or advertisers, this transaction will occur in connection with the site of the e-commerce partner, vendor or advertiser, not on the Site, and, as such, the financial and other personally identifiable information you provide is collected pursuant to and controlled by the privacy policy of such e-commerce partner, vendor or advertiser. Dealertrack is not responsible for such parties' privacy policies and we encourage you to familiarize yourself with the applicable privacy policy of the e-commerce site with which you transact business or to contact the operator of such site for more information. 

Please be aware that at times, at the request of or on behalf of our e-commerce partners, vendors or advertisers, Dealertrack may "pre-populate" forms with Your Information for your review, and, if you so choose, for submission to such e-commerce partners, vendors or advertisers; at other times, forms are pre-populated with Your Information in order to facilitate a transaction between you and Dealertrack with no such personally identifiable information being transmitted to Dealertrack partners, vendors or advertisers upon submission of such form. Accordingly, we encourage you to review each pre-populated form carefully before agreeing to submit your information to determine who is seeking to collect your information, and to familiarize yourself with the applicable privacy policy governing use of any personally identifiable information collected about you.

    * **Dealertrack Employees, Contractors and Agents** : Dealertrack may employ other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf, such as processing of payments, operating features of the Site, or hosting or maintaining our servers. These other companies may have access to your personal information as necessary to carry out their functions, but, absent your consent, they are not permitted to share that information with any third party (other than as necessary to perform their duties).
    * **Compliance With Applicable Law** : Dealertrack may also access and disclose Your Information in the event that we believe, in Dealertrack's discretion, that such action is reasonably necessary to comply with government requests; to enforce the Terms of Service or other published guidelines; to protect Dealertrack, its users or others; to respond to circumstances that we feel constitute an emergency; or as otherwise required or permitted by applicable law. Please be aware that, in connection with the foregoing, Dealertrack may provide information about you gathered through other sites controlled, owned or operated by Dealertrack or Dealertrack affiliates to the extent permitted under the applicable privacy policy governing collection and use of such information.
    * **Banner Ads**. Dealertrack sometimes uses individual data collected via the Site to "target" advertising - to decide which advertisements and sponsor messages to show to which members.
    * **Opt-In/Opt-Out Policy** : When you become a Site member or otherwise supply Dealertrack with Your Information in connection with the Site, or from time-to-time in Dealertrack's discretion, you may be asked to indicate whether you are interested in receiving marketing information from us about special offers in connection with the Site, Dealertrack and/or our advertisers and partners. You will also be provided with the opportunity to opt-out of receiving such offers. If you do choose to opt-out, you will not receive such communications. You may, of course, choose not to receive offers or other marketing communications from us or our third-party advertisers or partners as follows:
      * Upon becoming a Site member, you can choose to receive no marketing communications from us. Please be aware, however, that, even under this option, you may still receive an initial member welcome message, as well as communications as appropriate to inform you of changes to the Site, this Privacy Policy or other administrative matters.
      * At any time, you can follow a link provided in our newsletters or commercial email messages (but excluding e-commerce confirmations and other administrative emails) to unsubscribe from that particular mailing list or email service.
      * At any time, you can contact us through info@centraldispatch.com to have your contact preference changed to "Do Not Contact Me".
      * At any time, you can contact us through info@centraldispatch.com to opt out of having Your Information shared with our affiliates for their direct marketing purposes.

If you decide to contact us to change your contact preference to "Do Not Contact Me", Dealertrack will implement this change to your Site profile within ten (10) business days of your request. Please be aware that your requested change will not be effective until Dealertrack implements such change and that such requests will be implemented only in connection with your Site profile, and will not impact any preferences you may have made to any other site controlled, owned or operated by Dealertrack or its affiliates. In addition, please keep in mind that even if you opt-out from receiving communications from the Site, residual information about you will remain within Dealertrack databases, access logs and other records, which may or may not contain such personally identifiable information. The residual information will not be used for commercial purposes; however, Dealertrack reserves the right, from time to time, to re-contact former customers or users of the Site for administrative purposes or in order to comply with applicable law.

If you opt-in to the disclosure of Your Information to third parties, and you subsequently decide that you would like to discontinue receiving offers and other promotional materials from such third parties, you may need to contact those third parties directly in order to opt-out of further communications. 

Please note that Dealertrack reserves the right to change its opt-in/opt-out practices by modifying or updating this Privacy Policy as set forth above.

###### III. Accessing, Updating or Deleting Information Collected About You.

This Site also gives you the opportunity to modify or remove Your Information. You may do so by modifying your password-protected registered user information on the site. To the extent that such information is stored in our databases, we will respond to your changes immediately, although please understand that although this information, once deleted, is not available on the Site, that information may remain stored indefinitely in our backup and archival records. However, to the extent that such information is not stored in our databases, we cannot always ensure that these corrections or deletions will immediately reach such other databases.

Modify your registered user information on our Site; or send an email to info@centraldispatch.com.

###### IV. Security.

Dealertrack employs reasonable security measures consistent with standard industry practice, for information collected through this Site. However, you should exercise discretion with respect to the submission of any personal or financial information to this Site. Transmitting information via the Internet is never completely secure and, therefore, any information submitted may be intercepted, collected, used or disclosed by others. We cannot, and do not, guarantee that information supplied by users will not be accessed on our servers, or intercepted, collected, used or disclosed by others while being transmitted to or from the Site over the Internet.

Please remember that security of the username and password you create when you register with the Site, is your responsibility; we recommend that you do not share them with anyone. If you share your username and password, you are providing access to your personal information. You will be responsible for all uses of your registration, whether or not authorized by you. You agree to immediately notify Dealertrack of any unauthorized use of your username or password.

###### V. Links to Other Web Sites.

The Site may contain links to other Web sites, which may or may not be owned or operated by Dealertrack. All links to Web sites not part of our company are made without any representations or warranties relating to the integrity, security or legitimacy of such Web sites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of Web sites that are not owned and operated by Dealertrack, including such sites' use of any information (such as IP number, browser type or operating system) collected when visitors to the Site click through links to those sites. This Privacy Policy cannot and does not apply to external websites and, once you leave this Site, you are subject to that website’s privacy policies and procedures. We strongly encourage you to become familiar with the privacy practices and privacy policies of external Web sites before providing Your Information. If you have concerns about any linked Web site, we invite you to contact us.

###### VI. Intended for Adults Only.

This Site is for use by adults only. We will not solicit, collect or maintain personal information from children under the age of 18. In the event that a child under the age of 18 attempts to register as a member of our Site, we will NOT accept the registration and will delete information received from the child. In the event that a child posts personal information to the Site, we will attempt to delete that information once we become aware of it.

###### VII. Content.

Neither Dealertrack nor any third-party licensor shall have any liability for the accuracy or completeness of this service, any information contained therein, or any component thereof or for delays, inauthenticity, omissions, or other defects therein nor for any claims or losses arising therefrom or occasioned thereby, including, without limitation, any lost profits, indirect, special, or consequential damages. You agree not to use or permit anyone to use the information provided through the service for any unlawful or unauthorized purpose.

###### VIII. Legal Construction of this Privacy Policy.

This Privacy Policy and the Terms of Service provided on this Site shall be governed by, construed and enforced in accordance with the laws of the State of California, as it is applied to agreements entered into and to be performed entirely within such state, without regard to conflict of law principles. You agree that any cause of action you or Dealertrack brings to enforce this Privacy Policy or the Terms of Service, or in connection with any matters related to this Site and/or the Privacy Policy, shall be brought only in either the state or Federal courts located in San Diego County in the State of California. You agree to submit to the personal jurisdiction of the courts of the State of California for any cause of action arising out of this Privacy Policy. You agree to file any cause of action with respect to this Privacy Policy within one year after the cause of action arises. You agree that a cause of action filed after this date is barred.

If any provision of this Privacy Policy, or the application thereof to any person or circumstances, is held invalid or for any reason, unenforceable including, but not limited to, the warranty disclaimers and liability limitations, then such provision shall be deemed superseded by a valid, enforceable provision that matches, as closely as possible, the original provision, and the other provisions of this privacy statement shall remain in full force and effect. The failure of either party to insist upon strict performance of any provision of this privacy statement shall not be construed as a waiver of any provision or right. Unless expressly provided otherwise, this Privacy Policy and the Terms of Service presented on this Site comprise the entire agreement between you and Dealertrack with respect to the use of this Site and shall not be modified except in writing, signed by an authorized representative of Dealertrack.

###### IX. Contact Us.

If you have any questions about our company, this Site or this Privacy Policy, please contact us by clicking on the Contact Us link on this Site.
